Register of the Vladimir Pribylovskiĭ collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Biographical sources for Russian politicians, 1989-2006
  - Fedotov, Mikhail Aleksandrovich, 1991-1999 (Box-folder 7: 8)
  - Fedulova, Alevtina Vasil'evna, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 7: 8)
  - Feigin, Mark Zakharovich, 1994 (Box-folder 7: 8)
  - Feofanov, Iurii, Vasil'evich, 1993 (Box-folder 7: 8)
  - Fes'kov, Vladimir Afanas'evich, circa 1992 (Box-folder 7: 8)
  - Filatov, Leonid Alekseevich, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 7: 9)
  - Filatov, Sergei Aleksandrovich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 7: 9)
  - Filatov, Viktor Ivanovich, 1993 (Box-folder 7: 10)
  - Filiakin, Iurii Petrovich, 1993 (Box-folder 7: 10)
  - Filichev, Andrei Grigor'evich, 1999 (Box-folder 7: 10)
  - Filimonov, Vladimir L'vovich, 1993 (Box-folder 7: 10)
  - Filin, Mikhail Viktorovich, 1997 (Box-folder 7: 10)
  - Filin, Vladimir Ivanovich, 1995 (Box-folder 8: 10)
  - Filippov, Petr Sergeevich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 7: 11)
  - Filippov, Viktor Pavlovich, 1993 (Box-folder 7: 11)
  - Filippov, Vladimir Mikhailovich, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 7: 11)
  - Fil'shin, Gennadii Innokent'evich, 1992 (Box-folder 7: 12)
  - Fin'ko, Oleg Aleksandrovich, 1995 (Box-folder 7: 12)
  - Fomichev, Setrgei Rudol'fovich, 1992 (Box-folder 7: 12)
  - Fortov, Vladimir Evgen'evich, 1996 (Box-folder 7: 12)
  - Fradkov, Mikhail Efimovich, 1997 (Box-folder 7: 13)
  - Frolov, Ivan Timofeevich, 1990 (Box-folder 7: 13)
  - Frolov, Vladimir Afanas'evich, 1995 (Box-folder 7: 13)
  - Fronin, Vladislav Aleksandrovich, 1994 (Box-folder 7: 13)
  - Furman, Dmitrii Efimovich, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 7: 13)
  - Furmanov, Boris Aleksandrovich, 1992 (Box-folder 7: 13)
  - Furs, Aleksandr Vital'evich, 1996 (Box-folder 7: 13)
  - Gaer, Evdokiia Aleksandrovna, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 8: 1)
  - Gaidanov, Oleg Ivanovich, 1995 (Box-folder 8: 1)
  - Gaidar, Egor Timurovich, 1991-2001 (Box-folder 8: 2-6)
  - Gainutdinov (Gainutdin), Ravil', 1993 (Box-folder 8: 7)
  - Galazii, Grigorii Ivanovich, 1996 (Box-folder 8: 7)
  - Galkovskii, Dmitrii Evgen'evich, 1993 (Box-folder 8: 7)
  - Gal'chenko, Valerii Vladimirovich, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 8: 7)
  - Gantamirov (Gantemirov), Beslan (Bislan), 1999-2000 (Box-folder 8: 8)
  - Garapov, Al'bert Faritovich, 1992 (Box-folder 8: 8)
  - Gareev, Makhmut Akhmetovich, 1994-1999 (Box-folder 8: 8)
  - Gartsev, Oleg Ivanovich, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 8: 8)
  - Gazizullin, Farit, 1999 (Box-folder 8: 8)
  - Gdlian, Tel'man Khorenovich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 8: 9)
  - Gefter, Mikhail Iakovlevich, 1993 (Box-folder 8: 10)
  - Gekht, Iurii Grigor'evich, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 8: 10)
  - Gel'man, Marat Aleksandrovich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 8: 10)
  - Gel'man, Vladimir Iiakovlevich, 1992 (Box-folder 8: 10)
  - Generalov, Sergei Vladimirovich, 1998 (Box-folder 8: 10)
  - Geniatulin, Ravil' Faritovich, 1996 (Box-folder 8: 10)
  - Gerashchenko, Viktor Vladimirovich, 1990-2001 (Box-folder 8: 11)
  - Gerasimenko, Nikolai Fedorovich, 1996 (Box-folder 8: 12)
  - Gerasimov, Valerii Ivanovich, 1992 (Box-folder 8: 12)
  - Gerber, Alla Efremovna, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 8: 12)
  - Gerdt, Zinovii Efimovich, 1993 (Box-folder 8: 12)
  - Gerol'd, Iurii Anatol'evich, 1992 (Box-folder 8: 12)
  - Gidaspov, Boris Veniaminovich, 1995 (Box-folder 8: 12)
  - Gindeleev, Eduard Raisovich, 1999 (Box-folder 8: 12)
  - Ginzburg, Aleksandr Il'ich, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 8: 12)
  - Glazkov, Iurii Gennad'evich, 1996 (Box-folder 8: 13)
  - Glazunov, Il'ia Sergeevich, 1990-2000 (Box-folder 8: 13)
  - Glazychev, Viacheslav Leonidovich, 1999 (Box-folder 8: 14)
  - Glaz'ev, Sergei Iur'evich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 8: 14)
  - Glezer, Alksandr Davydovich, 1996 (Box-folder 8: 15)
  - Globa, Pavel Pavlovich, 1993 (Box-folder 8: 15)
  - Glotov, Sergei Aleksandrovich, 1993 (Box-folder 8: 15)
  - Glukhikh, Viktor Konstantinovich, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 8: 15)
  - Glushenkov, Anatolii Egorovich, 1995 (Box-folder 8: 15)
  - Gofshtein, Mikhail, 1996 (Box-folder 8: 15)
  - Golembiovskii, Igor' Nestorovich, 1992 (Box-folder 8: 15)
  - Golets, Sergei, 1995 (Box-folder 8: 15)
  - Golik, Iurii Vladimirovich, 1993 (Box-folder 8: 15)
  - Golikov, Viacheslav Mikhailovich, 1991 (Box-folder 8: 15)
  - Golitsyn, Andrei Kirillovich, 1996 (Box-folder 8: 15)
  - Golov, Anatolii Grigor'evich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 8: 16)
  - Golovin, Andrei Leonidovich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 8: 16)
  - Golovkov, Aleksei Leonardovich, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 8: 17)
  - Golovlev, Vladimir Ivanovich, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 8: 17)
  - Golushko, Nikolai Mikhailovich, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 8: 17)
  - Gonchar, Nikolai Nikolaevich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 8: 17)
  - Gonchar, Viktor Iosifovich, 1999 (Box-folder 8: 17)
  - Goncharov, Sergei Alekseevich, 1995 (Box-folder 8: 17)
  - Gontamakher, Evgenii Shlemovich, 1995 (Box-folder 8: 17)
  - Gorbachev, Mikhail Sergeevich, 1990-2000 (Box-folder 9: 1-6)
  - Gorbenko, Leonid Petrovich, 1999 (Box-folder 9: 7)
  - Gorchakov, Vasilii Ovidievich, 1995 (Box-folder 9: 7)
  - Gordon, Aleksandr Garrievich, 1995 (Box-folder 9: 7)
  - Gordon, Leonid Abramovich, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 9: 7)
  - Goriachev, Mark Leonidovich, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 9: 7)
  - Goriacheva, Svetlana Petrovna, 1991-1999 (Box-folder 9: 8)
  - Gorin, Dmitrii, 1995 (Box-folder 9: 8)
  - Gornyi, Iurii Gavrilovich, 1993 (Box-folder 9: 8)
  - Gostiukhin, Vladimir Vasil'evich, 1994 (Box-folder 9: 8)
  - Govorin, Boris Aleksandrovich, 1999 (Box-folder 9: 8)
  - Govorukhin, Sergei Stanislavovich, 1996 (Box-folder 9: 9)
  - Govorukhin, Stanislav Sergeevich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 9: 9)
  - Gozman, Leonid Iakovlevich, 1995 (Box-folder 9: 9)
  - Grachev, Andrei Serafimovich, 1991 (Box-folder 9: 10)
  - Grachev, Pavel Sergeevich, 1991-2001 (Box-folder 9: 10)
  - Grachev, Vladimir Aleksandrovich, 1990 (Box-folder 9: 11)
  - Granberg, Aleksandr Grigor'evich, 1986-1992 (Box-folder 9: 11)
  - Grebennikov, Valerii Vasil'evich, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 9: 11)
  - Grebenshchikov, Boris Borisovich, 1989-1996 (Box-folder 9: 12)
  - Grechnev, Viacheslav Viacheslavovich, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 9: 12)
  - Grigor'ev, Leonid Grigor'evich, 1992 (Box-folder 9: 12)
  - Grigor'ev, Vladimir Fedorovich, 1996 (Box-folder 9: 12)
  - Grigor'iants, Sergei Ivanovich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 9: 12)
  - Grishin, Viacheslav Leonidovich, 1993 (Box-folder 9: 13)
  - Grishkevich, Oleg Petrovich, 1990 (Box-folder 9: 13)
  - Gromov, Boris Vsevolodovich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 9: 14)
  - Gromov, Feliks Nikolaevich, 1993 (Box-folder 9: 15)
  - Groshev, Vladimir Pavlovich, 1996 (Box-folder 9: 15)
  - Grudnev, Vladimir Vasil'evich, 1992 (Box-folder 9: 15)
  - Gruzdev, Sergei Borisovich, 1999 (Box-folder 9: 15)
  - Gryzlov, Boris Viacheslavovich, 2000 (Box-folder 9: 15)
  - Gryzunov, Sergei Petrovich, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 9: 15)
  - Gubenko, Nikolai Nikolaevich, 1993-2000 (Box-folder 9: 16)
  - Gubkin, Igor' Vladimirovich, 1997 (Box-folder 9: 16)
  - Gulia-Ianovskii, Vsevolod Mikhailovich, circa 1992 (Box-folder 9: 16)
  - Gulii, Vitalii Valentinovich, circa 1990 (Box-folder 9: 16)
  - Gul'binskii, Nikolai Arsen'evich, 1991 (Box-folder 9: 16)
  - Gun'ko, Boris Mikhailovich, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 9: 16)
  - Gurevich, Leonid Borisovich, 1992 (Box-folder 9: 17)
  - Gurnov, Aleksandr Borisovich, 1992-1998 (Box-folder 9: 17)
  - Gurov, Aleksandr Ivanovich, 1994-2000 (Box-folder 9: 17)
  - Gurvits, Eduard Iosifovich, 1994 (Box-folder 9: 17)
  - Gur'ev, Vladimir, 1992 (Box-folder 9: 17)
  - Gusev, Georgii Georgievich, circa 1992 (Box-folder 9: 17)
  - Gusev, Iurii Nikolaevich, 1994 (Box-folder 9: 18)
  - Gusev, Pavel Nikolaevich, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 9: 18)
  - Gusev, Vladimir Vasil'evich, 1993 (Box-folder 9: 18)
  - Gusinskii, Vladimir Aleksandrovich, 1994-2001 (Box-folder 9: 18)
  - Gusliannikov, Vasilii Dmitrievich, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 9: 19)
  - Gusman, Iulii Solomonovich, 1994-2000 (Box-folder 9: 19)
  - Gustov, Vadim Anatol'evich, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 9: 19)
  - Gus'kov, Anatolii Vladimirovich, 1995 (Box-folder 9: 19)
  - Gutiontov, Pavel Semenovich, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 9: 19)
  - Gutseriev, Mikhail Safarbekovich, 1996-2000 (Box-folder 9: 19)
  - Iablokov, Aleksei Vladimirovich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 10: 1)
  - Iagodin, Gennadii Alekseevich, 1991 (Box-folder 10: 2)
  - Iag'ia, Vataniar Saidovich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 10: 2)
  - Iakobashvili, Zurab Andreevich, 1995 (Box-folder 10: 2)
  - Iakovenko, Igor Aleksandrovich, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 10: 2)
  - Iakovlev, Aleksandr, 1994 (Box-folder 10: 2)
  - Iakovlev, Aleksandr Nikolaevich, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 10: 3-4)
  - Iakovlev, Egor Vladimirovich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 10: 5)
  - Iakovlev, Iurii, 1995 (Box-folder 10: 5)
  - Iakovlev, Veniamin Al'bertovich, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 10: 6)
  - Iakovlev, Vladimir Anatol'evich, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 10: 6)
  - Iakovleva, Elena Stepanovna, 1994 (Box-folder 10: 6)
  - Iakubovskii, Dmitrii Olegovich, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 10: 7-9)
  - Iakunin, Gleb Pavlovich, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 10: 10)
  - Iakushev, Viktor Mikhailovich, 1995 (Box-folder 10: 10)
  - Iakushkin, Dmitrii Dmitrievich, 1999 (Box-folder 10: 10)
  - Ianaev, Gennadii Ivanovich, 1995 (Box-folder 10: 10)
  - Ianchev, Petr Viktorovich, 1997 (Box-folder 10: 10)
  - Iandarbiev, Zelimkhan Abdulmuslimovich, 1996 (Box-folder 10: 10)
  - Iankov, Kirill Vadimovich, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 10: 11)
  - Ianov, Aleksandr L'vovich, 1997 (Box-folder 10: 11)
  - Iaroshenko, Viktor Nikolaevich, 1999 (Box-folder 10: 11)
  - Iaroshinskaia-Egerskaia, Alla Aleksandrovna, 1994 (Box-folder 10: 11)
  - Iarov, Iurii Fedorovich, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 10: 11)
  - Iarygina, Tatiana Vladimirovna, 1996 (Box-folder 10: 12)
  - Iashin, Oleg Vladimirovich, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 10: 12)
  - Iasin, Evgenii Grigor'evich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 10: 13)
  - Iastrzhembskii, Sergei Vladimirovich, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 10: 14)
  - Iavlinskii, Grigorii Aleksesvich, 1991-1999 (Box-folder 10: 15-18)
  - Iazev, Valerii Afanas'evich, 2000 (Box-folder 11: 1)
  - Iazov, Dmitrii Timofeevich, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 11: 1)
  - Ignatenko, Vitalii Nikitich, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 11: 1)
  - Ignat'ev, Kirill Borisovich, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 11: 1)
  - Igrunov, Viacheslav Vladimirovich, 1993-2001 (Box-folder 11: 1)
  - Igumnov, Gennadii Viacheslavovich, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 11: 1)
  - Ikhlov, Boris Lazarevich, circa 1991 (Box-folder 11: 1)
  - Ikonnikov, Valerii Innokent'evich, 1992 (Box-folder 11: 1)
  - Iliukhin, Viktor Ivanovich, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 11: 2)
  - Iliumzhinov, Kirsan Nikolaevich, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 11: 3)
  - Iliushin, Viktor Vasil'evich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 11: 4)
  - Illesh, Andrei Vladimirovich, 1999 (Box-folder 11: 4)
  - Ilovaiskaia-Al'berti, Irina Alekseevna, 1993-2000 (Box-folder 11: 4)
  - Il'iushenko, Aleksei Nikolaevich, 1994-1998 (Box-folder 11: 4)
  - Indinok, Ivan Ivanovich, 1993 (Box-folder 11: 5)
  - Inozemtsev, Vladislav Leonidovich, 1992 (Box-folder 11: 5)
  - Ioann (Sychev, Ivan Matveevich), 1992 (Box-folder 11: 5)
  - Iodkovskii, Edmund Feliksovich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 11: 5)
  - Ioffe, Iulii Iakovlevich, 1994 (Box-folder 11: 5)
  - Isaev, Andrei Konstantinovich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 11: 5)
  - Isaev, Boris Mikhailovich, 1991 (Box-folder 11: 5)
  - Isaev, Grigorii Zinov'evich, circa 1990 (Box-folder 11: 5)
  - Isaichikov, Viktor Fedorovich, 1994 (Box-folder 11: 6)
  - Isakov, Vladimir Borisovich, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 11: 6)
  - Ishaev, Viktor Ivanovich, 1995 (Box-folder 11: 7)
  - Ishchenko, Evgenii Petrovich, 1995 (Box-folder 11: 7)
  - Iskander, Fazil' Abdulovich, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 11: 7)
  - Iskhakov, Kamil' Shamil'evich, 1999 (Box-folder 11: 7)
  - Ispravnikov, Viktor Olegovich, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 11: 7)
  - Iugin, Viktor Alekseevich, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 11: 8)
  - Iumashev, Valentin Borisovich, 1997 (Box-folder 11: 8)
  - Iurkov-Engel'gardt, Sergei Vol'evich, 1993 (Box-folder 11: 6)
  - Iur'ev, Dmitrii Aleksandrovich, 1993 (Box-folder 11: 8)
  - Iur'ev, Mikhail Zinov'evich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 11: 8)
  - Iushenkov, Sergei Nikolaevich, 1991-2001 (Box-folder 11: 9)
  - Iusufov, Igor' Khanukovich, 2001 (Box-folder 11: 10)
  - Iutkin, A., 1992 (Box-folder 11: 10)
  - Iuzbashev, Akop Borisovich, 1999 (Box-folder 11: 10)
  - Iuzhanov, Il'ia Arturovich, 2001 (Box-folder 11: 10)
  - Iuzvishin, Ivan Iosifovich, 1997 (Box-folder 11: 10)
  - Ivakin, Iurii Sergeevich, 1993 (Box-folder 11: 11)
  - Ivanchenko, Leonid Andreevich, 1996 (Box-folder 11: 11)
  - Ivanenko, Sergei Viktorovich, 1999 (Box-folder 11: 11)
  - Ivanenko, Viktor Valentinovich, 1993 (Box-folder 11: 11)
  - Ivaniuzhenkov, Boris Viktorovich, 1999 (Box-folder 11: 11)
  - Ivanov, Aleksandr Anatol'evich, 1999 (Box-folder 11: 11)
  - Ivanov, Igor' Sergeevich, 1999 (Box-folder 11: 11)
  - Ivanov, Iurii Sergeevich, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 11: 11)
  - Ivanov, Nikolai Veniaminovich, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 11: 12)
  - Ivanov, Viacheslav Vsevolodovich, 1993 (Box-folder 11: 12)
  - Ivanov, Vladimir Alekseevich, 1991 (Box-folder 11: 12)
  - Ivantsov, German Sergeevich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 11: 12)
  - Ivashchenko, Anatolii Igorevich, 1995 (Box-folder 11: 12)
  - Ivashko, Vladimir Antonovich, 1990 (Box-folder 11: 12)
  - Ivchenkov, Sergei Sergeevich, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 11: 12)
  - Iver, Vasilii Mikhailovich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 11: 12)
  - Kadannikov, Vladimir Vasil'evich, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 11: 13)
  - Kadyrov, Rafis Faizovich, 1993 (Box-folder 11: 13)
  - Kagalovskii, Konstantin Grigor'evich, 1991 (Box-folder 11: 13)
  - Kagarlitskii, Boris Iul'evich, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 11: 13)
  - Kaiunov, Oleg Nikolaevich, 1995 (Box-folder 11: 14)
  - Kalamanov, Viktor Avdashevich, 1999 (Box-folder 11: 14)
  - Kaliuzhnyi, Viktor Ivanovich, 1999 (Box-folder 11: 14)
  - Kalmanovich, Shabtai Genrikhovich, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 11: 14)
  - Kalugin, Oleg Dmitrievich, 1991-1997 (Box-folder 12: 1)
  - Kantor, Oleg Iaroslavovich, 1995 (Box-folder 12: 2)
  - Kara-Murza, Sergei Georgievich, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 12: 5)
  - Karabanov, Evgenii Pavlovich, 1996 (Box-folder 12: 2)
  - Karaganov, Sergei Aleksandrovich, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 12: 2)
  - Karaulov, Andrei Viktorovich, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 12: 2)
  - Kardail'skii, Vladimir Aleksandrovich, 1992 (Box-folder 12: 3)
  - Kardin, V., 1993 (Box-folder 12: 3)
  - Karelin, Aleksandr Aleksandrovich, 1999 (Box-folder 12: 3)
  - Karpov, Petr Anatol'evich, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 12: 3)
  - Karpov, Stanislav Anatol'evich, 1993 (Box-folder 12: 3)
  - Kasatonov, Igor' Vladimirovich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 12: 3)
  - Kashin, Vladimir, 2000 (Box-folder 12: 4)
  - Kashpirovskii, Anatolii Mikhailovich, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 12: 4)
  - Kasparov, Garri Kimovich, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 12: 4)
  - Kataev, Dmitrii Ivanovich, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 12: 5)
  - Kazakov, Aleksandr Ivanovich, 1996 (Box-folder 12: 5)
  - Kazakov, Vasilii Ivanovich, 1993 (Box-folder 12: 5)
  - Kazannik, Aleksei Ivanovich, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 12: 5)
  - Kazantsev, Viktor Germanovich, 1997 (Box-folder 12: 6)
  - Kazarov, Oleg Vladimirovich, 1996 (Box-folder 12: 6)
  - Kazhegel'din, Akezhan Margzhanovich, 1999 (Box-folder 12: 6)
  - Kaziev, Ragim Gasanovich, 1995 (Box-folder 12: 6)
  - Kezina, Liubov' Petrovna, 1999 (Box-folder 12: 6)
  - Khachilaev, Nadirshakh Mugadovich, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 12: 7)
  - Khadzhiev, Salambek Naibovich, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 12: 7)
  - Khagazheev, Dzhonson Talovich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 12: 7)
  - Khakamada, Irina Mutsuovna, 1993-2000 (Box-folder 12: 8)
  - Khakimov, Rafail Sibgatovich, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 12: 9)
  - Khandruev, Aleksandr Andreevich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 12: 9)
  - Khapsirokov, Nazir, 1999 (Box-folder 12: 9)
  - Khardaeva, Lidiia Kazakovna, 1991 (Box-folder 12: 9)
  - Kharichev, Igor' Aleksandrovich, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 12: 9)
  - Kharitonov, Nikolai Mikhailovich, 1996 (Box-folder 12: 9)
  - Khasbulatov, Ruslan Imranovich, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 12: 10-14)
  - Khatsenkov, Georgii Fedorovich, 1999 (Box-folder 13: 1)
  - Khinshtein, Aleksandr Evseevich, 1999 (Box-folder 13: 1)
  - Khizha, Georgii Sergeevich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 13: 1)
  - Khloponin, Aleksandr Gennadievich, 1996 (Box-folder 13: 2)
  - Khlystun, Viktor Nikolaevich, 1992-1998 (Box-folder 13: 2)
  - Khodorkovskii, Mikhail Borisovich, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 13: 2)
  - Khomiakov, Aleksandr Vadimovich, circa 1995 (Box-folder 13: 2)
  - Khomiakov, Petr Mikhailovich, 1993 (Box-folder 13: 3)
  - Khomiakov, Valerii Alekseevich, 1991 (Box-folder 13: 3)
  - Khramov, Sergei Vladimirovich, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 13: 3)
  - Khristenko, Viktor Borisovich, 1999 (Box-folder 13: 3)
  - Kichikhin, Aleksandr Nikolaevich, 1993 (Box-folder 13: 4)
  - Kim, Evgenii Nikolaevich, 1991 (Box-folder 13: 4)
  - Kinilev, Vladimir Georgievich, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 13: 4)
  - Kinstler, Eduard, 1993 (Box-folder 13: 4)
  - Kirienko, Sergei Vladimirovich, 1999 (Box-folder 13: 4)
  - Kirill (Gundiaev, Vladimir Mikhailovich), 1997-1998 (Box-folder 13: 4)
  - Kirillov, Vitalii Vladimirovich, 2000 (Box-folder 13: 5)
  - Kirillov, Vladimir Ivanovich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 13: 5)
  - Kisilev, Aleksandr Aleksandrovich, 1989 (Box-folder 13: 5)
  - Kisilev, Mikhail Mikhailovich, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 13: 5)
  - Kisilev, Oleg Vladimirovich, 1995 (Box-folder 13: 5)
  - Kisin, Vadim Vital'evich, 1996 (Box-folder 13: 5)
  - Kisliuk, Mikhail Borisovich, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 13: 5)
  - Kivelidi, Ivan Kharlampievich, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 13: 6)
  - Klebanov, Vladimir Aleksandrovich, 1993 (Box-folder 13: 7)
  - Kliamkin, Igor' Moiseevich, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 13: 7)
  - Klimen't'ev, Andrei Anatol'evich, 1997 (Box-folder 13: 7)
  - Klimin, Anatolii Vladimirovich, 1999 (Box-folder 13: 7)
  - Kliuchnikov, Vitalii Alekseevich, 1993 (Box-folder 13: 7)
  - Klochkov, Igor' Evgen'evich, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 13: 7)
  - Klykov, Viacheslav Mikhailovich, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 13: 7)
  - Kobets, Konstantin Ivanovich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 13: 8)
  - Kobylkin, Vasilii Fedorovich, 1998 (Box-folder 13: 8)
  - Kogan, Evgenii Vladimirovich, 1992 (Box-folder 13: 8)
  - Kogan, Vladimir Igorevich, 1999 (Box-folder 13: 8)
  - Kokh, Al'fred Reingol'dovich, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 13: 9)
  - Kokoshin, Andrei Afanas'evich, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 13: 9)
  - Kokun'ko, Georgii Valentinovich, 1991 (Box-folder 13: 9)
  - Kolbasiuk, Vitalii, 1993 (Box-folder 13: 9)
  - Kolerov, Il'ia Andreevich, 1996 (Box-folder 13: 9)
  - Kolesnikov, Andrei Vladimirovich, 1993 (Box-folder 13: 9)
  - Kolesnikov, Vladimir Il'ich, 1995 (Box-folder 13: 10)
  - Kolganov, Andrei Ivanovich, 1993 (Box-folder 13: 10)
  - Kolodizhner, Asia, 1995 (Box-folder 13: 10)
  - Komchatov, Vladimir Fedorovich, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 13: 10)
  - Komissarov, Viacheslav Sergeevich, 1991 (Box-folder 13: 11)
  - Konanykhin, Aleksandr Pavlovich, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 13: 11)
  - Konchalovskii, Andrei Sergeevich, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 13: 12)
  - Kondrashev, Boris Petrovich, 1993 (Box-folder 13: 12)
  - Kondratenko, Nikolai Ignatovich, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 13: 12)
  - Kondratov, Vladimir Aleksandrovich, 1991 (Box-folder 13: 12)
  - Koniakhin, Gennadii Vladimirovich, 1999 (Box-folder 13: 12)
  - Konovalov, Leonid Valentinovich, circa 1993 (Box-folder 13: 12)
  - Konstantinov, Il'ia Vladislavovich, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 13: 12)
  - Kon'kov, Igor' Viktorovich, 1992 (Box-folder 13: 12)
  - Kop'ev, Viacheslav Vsevolodovich, 1999 (Box-folder 13: 3)
  - Korchagin, Viktor Ivanovich, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 13: 13)
  - Korchinskii, Dmitrii Aleksandrovich, 1995 (Box-folder 13: 13)
  - Koriakina, Tat'iana Ivanovna, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 13: 13)
  - Korneeva, Zoia Ivanovna, 1993 (Box-folder 13: 13)
  - Kornilova, Zoia Afanas'evna, 1992 (Box-folder 13: 13)
  - Korobchenko, Viktor Alekseevich, 1993 (Box-folder 13: 13)
  - Korolev, Oleg Andreevich, 1996 (Box-folder 13: 13)
  - Korotich, Vitalii Alekseevich, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 13: 14)
  - Korovikov, Igor' Valentinovich, 1991 (Box-folder 13: 14)
  - Korsetov, Vladimir Evgen'evich, 1993 (Box-folder 13: 14)
  - Korzhakov, Aleksandr Vasil'evich, 1991-1997 (Box-folder 13: 15)
  - Kosachev, Konstantin Iosifovich, 2000 (Box-folder 14: 1)
  - Koshliakov, Lev Sergeevich, 1999 (Box-folder 14: 1)
  - Koshman, Nikolai Pavlovich, 1999 (Box-folder 14: 1)
  - Koshmarov, Aleksei Iur'evich, 1999 (Box-folder 14: 1)
  - Kosolapov, Richard Ivanovich, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 14: 1)
  - Kostanov, Iurii Artem'evich, 1993 (Box-folder 14: 1)
  - Kostenko, Boris Igorevich, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 14: 1)
  - Kostikov, Viacheslav Vasil'evich, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 14: 1)
  - Kostin, Andrei Leonidovich, 1996 (Box-folder 14: 2)
  - Kostromin, Sergei Vladimirovich, 1996 (Box-folder 14: 2)
  - Kotelkin, Aleksandr Ivanovich, 1997 (Box-folder 14: 2)
  - Kotenev, Aleksandr Aleksandrovich, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 14: 2)
  - Kotenkov, Aleksandr Andreevich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 14: 3)
  - Kotov, Igor' Mikhailovich, 2000 (Box-folder 14: 3)
  - Kovalev, Aleksei Anatol'evich, 1997 (Box-folder 14: 3)
  - Kovalev, Nikolai Dmitrievich, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 14: 3)
  - Kovalev, Sergei Adamovich, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 14: 4)
  - Kovalevskii, Vladimir Antonovich, 1993 (Box-folder 14: 5)
  - Kozhakin, Evgenii Mikhailovich, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 14: 5)
  - Kozhemiakin, Vladimir Ivanovich, 1991 (Box-folder 14: 5)
  - Kozhikhov, Mikhail Iur'evich, 1999 (Box-folder 14: 5)
  - Kozhin, Vladimir Igorevich, 2001 (Box-folder 14: 5)
  - Kozhinov, Vadim Valerianovich, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 14: 5)
  - Kozlenok, Andrei Vladimirovich, 1999 (Box-folder 14: 5)
  - Kozlov, Andrei Andreevich, 1997 (Box-folder 14: 5)
  - Kozlov, Evgenii Aleksandrovich, 1993 (Box-folder 14: 5)
  - Kozyrev, Andrei Vladimirovich, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 14: 6)
  - Kraiko, Aleksandr Nikolaevich, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 14: 7)
  - Krasavchenko, Sergei Nikolaevich, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 14: 7)
  - Krasheninnikov, Pavel Vladimirovich, 1999 (Box-folder 14: 7)
  - Krasikov, Anatolii Andreevich, 1993 (Box-folder 14: 7)
  - Krasnov, Aleksandr Viktorovich, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 14: 8)
  - Krasnov, Petr Stepanovich, 1993 (Box-folder 14: 8)
  - Krasulia, Vasilii Aleksandrovich, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 14: 9)
  - Kravchenko, Leonid Petrovich, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 14: 9)
  - Kreimer, Mikhail Dmitrievich, 1999 (Box-folder 14: 9)
  - Kriger, Vera Frantsevna, 1991 (Box-folder 14: 9)
  - Kriuchkov, Anatolii Viktorovoch, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 14: 9)
  - Kruglov, Anatolii Sergeevich, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 14: 10)
  - Kryshtanovskaia, Ol'ga Viktorovna, 1995 (Box-folder 14: 10)
  - Kucher, Stanislav Aleksandrovich, 1995 (Box-folder 14: 10)
  - Kudimova, Marina Vladimirovna, 1993 (Box-folder 14: 10)
  - Kudiukin, Pavel Mikhailovich, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 14: 10)
  - Kudrin, Andrei Leonidovich, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 14: 11)
  - Kulakov, Aleksandr Edauardovich, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 14: 11)
  - Kulikov, Aleksandr Dmitrievich, 1996 (Box-folder 14: 12)
  - Kulikov, Aleksandr Nikolaevich, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 14: 12)
  - Kulikov, Anatolii Sergeevich, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 14: 12)
  - Kulikov, Georgii Viktorovich, 1996 (Box-folder 14: 13)
  - Kulikov, Nikolai Vasil'evich, 1999 (Box-folder 14: 13)
  - Kuniaev, Stanislav Iur'evich, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 14: 13)
  - Kuptsov, Valentin Aleksandrovich, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 14: 13)
  - Kuraev, Andrei Viacheslavovich, 1993 (Box-folder 14: 13)
  - Kurakin, Boris Evgen'evich, 1993 (Box-folder 14: 13)
  - Kurginian, Sergei Ervandovich, 1991-1999 (Box-folder 14: 14)
  - Kuriachev, Mikhail Vasil'evich, 1991 (Box-folder 14: 15)
  - Kurkova, Bella Alekseevna, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 14: 15)
  - Kushnar', Aleksandr Leonidovich, 1996 (Box-folder 14: 15)
  - Kutepov, Evgenii Aleksandrovich, 1996 (Box-folder 14: 15)
  - Katul'skii, Evgenii Danilovich, 1996 (Box-folder 14: 15)
  - Kuznechevskii, Vladimir Dmitrievich, 1992 (Box-folder 14: 15)
  - Kuznetsov, Anatolii Leonidovich, 1996 (Box-folder 14: 15)
  - Kuznetsov, Igor' Borisovich, 1994 (Box-folder 14: 15)